Guide to the Robert Kraushaar papers, [ca. 1970-1990]
Kraushaar, Robert papers
- Docklands Joint Committee and the Joint Port Trade Development Committee. "Joint Statement by the Docklands Joint Committee and the Joint Trade Development Committee to the Secretary of State for the Envrionment and the Secretary of State for Industry. Docks 204." London: Docklands Joint Committee and the Joint Port Trade Development Committee, 1977., March 31, 1977; Document (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Docklands Joint Committee. "Standing Orders. Docks 122." London: Docklands Joint Committee, 1976., May 7, 1976; Document (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Docklands Joint Committee Finance Officer. "Docklands Annual Budget 1976/77 P.2 Programme. Docks 109." London: Docklands Joint Committee, 1975., December 29, 1975; Document (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Photocopy: 2 page
- Docklands Joint Committee Finance Officer. "Return of Expenditure for Seven Months Ended 31 October 1975. Docks 110." London: Docklands Joint Committee, 1975., December 29, 1975; Document (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Docklands Development Team. "Draft Docklands Strategy - The Public Response. Docks 132." London: Docklands Joint Committee, 1976., July 7, 1976; Document (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Docklands Development Team. "Overall Summary of the Response to the Draft Docklands Strategy and Proposed Amendments Resulting. Docks 130." London: Docklands Joint Committee, 1976., July 8, 1976; Document (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Warren, J. J. (Chief Executive of London Borough of Newham). "Consultative Machinery for Facilitiating Discussion of Matters." Letter to Director of Dockalnds Development Team. London: London Borough of Newham, 1976., April 29, 1976; Document (Box 1, Folder 24)
- [no author provided] "London's Area of Opportunity." London: Docklands Development Team, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Pamphlet: 1 page
- Peckham. "Docklands Joint Committee Index of Documents." London: Docklands Joint Committee, 1977., August 12, 1988; Document (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Document with handwritten letter attached: 20 pages
- Evans, Beryl. "Opening the Way to Docklands." London: Greater London Council, 1977., June 2, 1977; Document (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Document: 2 pages
- Sheffield City Council. Positive Action for Women Project: Final Report. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, 1984, October 22, 1984; Document (Box 2, Folder 1)
  75 pages
- City of Sheffield. A Local Enterprise Board for Sheffield. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1981., December 21, 1981; Document (Box 2, Folder 1)
  13 pages
- City of Sheffield. Sheffield Employment Plan. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, c. 1987, c. 1987; Document (Box 2, Folder 1)
  28 pages
- City of Sheffield: Employment Programme Committee. Municipal Music Services and Recording Project "Sheffield Music Factory". Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1984., July 23, 1984; Document (Box 2, Folder 2)
  50 pages
- City of Sheffield: Employment Department. Aids to Enterprises: Review and Proposed Strategy. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no date provided], [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 2)
  16 pages
- Baker, Will; Coulson, Andrew. The Sheffield City Council Employment Department. Sheffield, England: [no publisher provided], 1985-89, c. 1985-89; Document (Box 2, Folder 2)
  38 pages
- Benington, John. Talk at Sheffield Conference. Sheffield, England: [no publisher provided], [no date provided], [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 2)
  10 pages
- Healey, Patsy. A Series of Lectures for Centenary Year: Whither the City -- Which Way for Sheffield?Sheffield, England: University of Newcastle, c. 1993, c. 1993; Document (Box 2, Folder 2)
  3 pages
- City of Sheffield. The Role of the Business Community. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1988., November 1988; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- City of Sheffield. Agreement Between the Sheffield City Council and the Sheffield Urban Development Corporation. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1988., August 19, 1988; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
  4 pages
- Sheffield Census. Workplace Data for Sheffield. Sheffield, England: Sheffield Census, 1981, 1981; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
  15 pages
- City of Sheffield. Draft Job Description. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
  2 pages
- Blunkett, David - City of Sheffield. Draft Report - Options for the Future for Maintaining Services, Jobs, and Local Control. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, 1985, June 27, 1985; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
  5 pages
- City of Sheffield. Sheffield City Council Employment Scheme. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982., April 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
  8 pages
- Blunkett, David - City of Sheffield. Paper to Labor Group. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, [no date provided], [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Billings, Alan - Budget Sub-Committee, City of Sheffield. The Two-Year Strategy. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, 1985, June 26, 1985; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
  7 pages
- Walker, Alan; Westergaard, John. After Redundancy: a study of some responses to unemployment in the Sheffield steel industry. Sheffield, England: University of Sheffield, 1980, December 1980; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Blunkett, David - City of Sheffield. Alternative Economic Policies - A Socialist Local Government Response. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, 1981, February 1981; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
  9 pages
- Sheffield District Labour Party Employment Manifesto Working Group. Meeting Agenda. Sheffield, England: Sheffield District Labour Party Employment Manifesto Working Group, 1981., November 1981; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Darwin, J.; Downs, L. - Employment Department. Darwin/Downs Revised Departmental Structure. Sheffield, England: Employment Department of Sheffield City Council, 1982., December 1, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- City of Sheffield. Economic Development, Enforced Competition and Subsequent Matters - Departmental Responsibilities. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, 1987., October 1987; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Guiton, Ed. Notes on Departmental Organisation. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, [no date provided], [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- [no author provided] Chapel-Green Community Project. Sheffield, England: [no publisher provided], 1984., 1984; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Sheffield City Council Shop Stewards and Union Representatives. Defending Sheffield: The Shop Steward's Response. Sheffield, England: Shop Stewards and Union Representatives, 1984, January 18, 1984; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Douglas, John. Employment and Unemployment (extracts). Sheffield, England: [no publisher provided], 1981, August 3, 1981; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- The Sheffield Business Venture. The Sheffield Business Venture Helps Small Businesses To Start, Grow, and Prosper. Sheffield, England: The Sheffield Business Venture, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  1 page
- Benington, John - Employment Department, City of Sheffield. A Three Year Resource Plan to Meet Changing Needs. Sheffield, England: Employment Department, 1984., September 26, 1984; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Brown, Michael Barratt - City of Sheffield. A Local Enterprise Board for Sheffield/South Yorkshire. Sheffield, England: Northern College, 1981., July 1981; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Greater London Council. Report for Industry and Employment Committee Finance and General Purposes Committee. Sheffield, England: Greater London Council, 1982., July 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 3)
  12 pages
- [no author provided] Review of the Council's Organisation and Management. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, 1983., May 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Structured document reviewing the structures and policies of the City Council. Includes diagrams of council structure. 19 pages.
- [no author provided] Employment Department Employees. City of Sheffield, 1983., May 19, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  List of employee titles, names, and extensions. 2 pages
- Guiton, Ed. Notes on Departmental Organisation. Sheffield, England: Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, [no date provided], [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Concise document outlining the present teams in the employment department with suggestions for new organization. 2 pages
- [no author provided] Departmental Review. Sheffield, England: Employment Department of City Council, 1982, December 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Review proposing specific tasks for departmental staff. 4 pages
- Benington, Jon. Memo to the Manpower Services Commission, Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982, June 18, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Letter proposing a structured method of providing part-time, socially useful work for the unemployed.3 pages
- [no author provided] Sheffield City Council Employment Scheme. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982., April 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  3 memos outlining and describing a proposal to create 1000 jobs in Sheffield. 6 pages
- [no author provided] Report of the Special Sub-Committee to Review the Council's Organisation and Management. Sheffield, England: Sheffield City Council, 1983., c.Jan/Feb-83; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Descriptions of structure, recommendations for new organization within the Council. Includes appendix with review memos of specific departments and diagram of committee structure. 15 pages
- Benington, Jon. City of Sheffield - Memorandum. Sheffield, England: City Council of Sheffield, 1982, May 12, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Agenda for Employment Department meeting. Attached departmental reviews of structure and programmes. 29 pages
- Darwin, John. Proposals for Co-ordinating Group Duties in Employment Department. Sheffield, England: City Council of Sheffield, 1983., September 5, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Proposals for the duties of a co-ordinating group in the employment department. 2 copies. 2 pages each.
- Benington, John. Review of the Employment Department's Work in the Pilot Phase and Plans And Priorities for the Next Year. Sheffield, England: City Council of Sheffield, 1983., April 25, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Proposed structure for a report on the pilot phase of Employment Department's employment project. Attached memo from Benington to Councilor Blunkett. 2 pages
- [no author provided] Meeting Agenda. Sheffield, England: Sheffield District Labour Party Employment Manifesto Working Group, 1981., November 9, 1981; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Agenda for Employment Manifesto Working Group; Minutes from previous meeting. 2 copies. 3 pages total
- Benington, John. Memo for Editorial Group Meeting. Sheffield, England: Employment Department, Mary 23, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Proposed agenda for employment department meeting with questions for review of projects. 4 pages
- Guiton, Ed. Discussion Paper for Business Start-up Proposals. Sheffield, England. Employment Department, May 20, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Proposals for applications of assistance from Sheffield Enterprises for businesses. 3 pages
- Darwin, J; Downs, L; Employment Department. Darwin/Downs Revised Departmental Structure. Sheffield, England: Employment Department of Sheffield City Council, 1982., December 17, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Descriptions and diagrams of departmental structure of the Employment Department. 5 pages
- Blunkett, David; Edge, Geoff. Exchange Between Blunkett and Councillor Edge about Direct Investment by West Midlands County Council. Sheffield, England: County Council of West Midlands and Sheffield City Council, 1982., May 6, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Memo from Edge to Blunkett describing proposed industrial investment for job development. Blunkett's response included. 7 pages
- [no author provided] Agreement Between the Sheffield City Council and the Sheffield Urban Development Corporation. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1988., August 19, 1988; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Agreement between Sheffield City Council and UDC to reduce unemployment. 4 pages
- Salisbury, Brian. Memo to John Benington with Proposals for Unit for Development of Alternative Products. Sheffield, England: Employment Department, 1982., Sptember 27, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Memo to Benington with attached proposals written by Holroyde in Mar-81. Proposed Polytechnic Units. 3 pages
- P., Mick [no other information provided]. Memo to Beningto: Departmental Review. Sheffield, England: Employment Department. 1985, October 5, 1985; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Handwritten and photocopied memo to Benington with suggestions for department review. 1 page
- Benington, John. Abolition: 1,400 more jobs - L60m cost says report. (1984) Municipal Journal, 252., February 24, 1984; Article (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Journal article describing the addition of public service jobs to Sheffield and the resulting government costs. 1 page
- [no author provided] Proposed Structure of the Employment Department., c. May 1983; Draft Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Handwritten diagram and descriptions of proposed structure of employment department. 3 pages
- Aids to Enterprises: Sectional Review, Second Draft., May 5, 1983; Draft Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Handwritten and photocopied aid to enterprises. 3 pages
- [no author provided] Meeting March 1st Agenda., March 1, 1984?; Document (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Meeting Agenda with attached administrative, financial, and managerial structure diagram. 3 pages
- [no author provided] Mineworkers' Pension Scheme. Sheffield, England, 1981., May 11, 1981; Document (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Charts and tables of stocks, properties, sources of funds -- meant to determine pension for mineworkers. 3 pages
- [no author provided] Memorandum: An Invitation to Contribute to a Review of the Council's Organisation and Management. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., February 1, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 5)
  An invitation to employees to participate in a discussion on the reorganisation of the employment department. Attached is a description of current duties. 7 pages
- Director of Environmental Health, Sheffield England. Memorandum: Review of the Council's Organisation and Management. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., January 31, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Memo with attached extended review of needs for change within the Council. 4 pages
- [no author provided] CMU and Research CO-Ordination. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Proposal for the reorganisation of the CMU. Attached diagram of committee structure and duties. Attached "Extract from 'Public Participation in Local Services'". 5 pages.
- Benington, John. Memorandum: Meeting Agenda for Preliminary Meeting of Employment Department Co-ordinating Group. Sheffield, England, City of Sheffield, 1982., May 12, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Agenda for meeting to discuss work of the employment department. 4 pages
- [no author provided] Consultation and Co-ordination within the Employment Department. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982., June 25, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Proposals for functions of employment department. 3 pages
- Darwin, John. Departmental Review-Paper. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982, November 1, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Brief proposals for changes in department structure. 1 page
- Coulson, Andrew. Departmental Reorganisation. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982., November 9, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Proposals for reorganisation of Employment Department. 3 pages
- Guiton, Ed. Notes on Departmental Organisation. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Outline of teams within the employment department. 3 pages
- [no author provided] Co-ordinating Group: Review of Departmental Decision-Making and Structure. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982., November 17, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Proposals for decision-making roles of executives in employment department. 2 pages
- Benington, John. Planning and Decision-Making In Phase Two of the Department's Work. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., May 3, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Outlines of meeting decisions, descriptions of program failures and successes within employment department. 3 drafts included. 13 pages
- Cromar, Pete. Review of Departmental Structures. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982., November 18, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Summary of review of employment department at previous meeting. 1 page
- Cromar, Pete. Planning and Decision-Making in the Employment Department. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., May 12, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Outline of decisions/proposals within employment department. 2 pages
- [no author provided] Comments on Council Review of Research, Information, and Strategy. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., March 25, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Review of research strategies and sources for department changes. 4 pages
- [no author provided] Policy Review Sub-Committee Comments. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., June 13, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Handwritten reviews of policy reports. 2 pages
- Benington, John. Memorandum: Review of the Council's Organisation and Management. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., February 14, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Comments on department decisions. Attached outline of proposals for second phase of changes. 3 pages
- Benington, John. Review of the Department's Work in the Pilot Phase - Meeting Minutes April 25, 1983. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., May 9, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  List of Department agreements. 2 pages
- Employment Department, Sheffield, England. Equal Opportunities Project Team Organisation and Management Review. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., March 10, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Outline of aspects of equal opportunity proposals in employment department. 3 pages
- [no author provided] Report of the Housing Seminar Held on Friday 16th July 1982 at Granville College. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982., July 27, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Description of decisions and discussion at Budget Sub-Committee and other members' meeting. Attached attendance list. 4 pages
- [no author provided] Introduction to Review of the Council's Organisation and Management. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., May 1, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Table of Contents for review of Council's organisation and introduction. 3 pages
- Benington, John. Memorandum: Preparation for Meeting on May 26th and 27th. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., May 23, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Brief Memo to Co-ordinating Group to plan upcoming meeting. 1 page
- [no author provided] Proposed Agenda: Meeting of Editorial Group. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., May 1, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Meeting schedule and agenda to review the work of the department in the first year and consider next phase. 2 pages
- [no author provided] Checklist of Questions for Review of Projects. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Questions to review department projects. 1 page
- [no author provided] Employment Services. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Text Excerpt (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Photocopied pages with lists of ways to generate economic build. 5 pages
- [no author provided] Municipal Enterprise - Review of First Year's Work. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., May 6, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Background, review, and proposals for the future of the municipal enterprise of City Council. 6 pages
- Kennaway, Ian. Aids to Enterprises - Discussion Paper. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no date provided], [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Conditions and Agreements for job-generating enterprises to receive Financial Assistance. 7 pages
- [no author provided] Objectives for Employment Research and Resource Unit. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Objectives for Resource Unit, Technology programme, Enterprise Team, and Employment Training. Descriptive goals for Industrial Development. 5 pages
- [no author provided] New Technology and Product Development. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., April 20, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  First Draft of one year's work on new technology for job generation by the Employment Department. 4 pages
- [no author provided] Training for Employment. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., May 5, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Proposals and actions needed for specific job training by employment department. 7 pages
- [no author provided] Report to Co-ordinating Group Meeting - 22 April 1983: Departmental Review. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., April 22, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Year's review of Equal Opportunity employment in department, needed actions for upcoming year. 7 pages
- Employment Department, Sheffield, England. Conclusions to Report of Sheffield's Economic Crisis. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1984., July 1, 1984; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Outline of job crisis, some propositions for rectifying the situation. 2 pages
- [no author provided] Industrial Development by the Council. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1983., May 6, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Background, Programme descriptions, Issues and concerns of Industrial Development by the Council. Attached memo from Fred Swinden to John Benington. 3 pages
- [no author provided] Employment Research and Resources Unit. Sheffield, England:City of Sheffield, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Descriptions of the work of Employment Research and Resources Unit. Attached outline of unit's purpose. 7 pages
- Guiton, Ed. Discussion Paper. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no year provided]., May 20, ?; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Paper for meeting outlining some of the schemes for job-generation and private sector investment that have been and will be implemented. 6 pages
- Benington, John. Letter to All Members of the Manpower Services Commission. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, 1982., June 18, 1982; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Letter suggesting additional help for the unemployed; proposals. 3 pages
- [no author provided] Employment Department - An Initial Outline. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no year provided]., [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Outline of purpose and duties of Employment Department. Attached diagram of department structure. 5 pages
- [no author provided] Employment Department - Programme Areas. Sheffield, Engladn: City of Sheffield, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Programme objectives and descriptions within Employment Department. 6 pages
- [no author provided] Britain Feels the Squeeze. Sheffield, England: City of Sheffield, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Public flier depicting unemployment and other economic factors through bar graphs. 1 page
- Goodwin, Mark. Locality and Local State: Sheffield's Economic Policy. Sussex: The University of Sussex, 1986., February 1, 1986; Research Paper (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Working university paper using Sheffield's economic policy to study local government strategies. 50 pages